[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1853, this jeans producer started the first denim clothing business, intended to supply the miners in California with strong clothing.", "correct_answer": "Levi Strauss", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee Jeans", "Wrangler", "D  G"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the Euro currency first launched?", "correct_answer": "January 1999", "incorrect_answers": ["January 1990", "January 1985", "January 1994"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Pretty Woman, Edward Lewis takes the character portrayed by Julia Roberts to see which opera?", "correct_answer": "La Traviata", "incorrect_answers": ["MacBeth", "Madame Butterfly", "Rigoletto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The San Francisco earthquake is one of the most ill-famed earthquakes in history.  It happened in this year.", "correct_answer": "1906", "incorrect_answers": ["1908", "1916", "1910"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name is commonly used for the hat worn by academics, also known as square academic cap?", "correct_answer": "Mortarboard", "incorrect_answers": ["Flathat", "Table hat", "Board cap"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What phobia is characterized by fear of pins?", "correct_answer": "Enetophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Entomophobia", "Ephebiphobia", "Emetophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Suspiria was about a fancy ballet academy run by a coven of witches.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "As explained in Back to the Future, what was Doc allergic to?", "correct_answer": "synthetic material", "incorrect_answers": ["pine tree needles", "certain animals", "dairy products"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The long body of the church Hagia Irene in Istanbul (former Constantinople) is covered by two domes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A mother will give birth to this kind of twins if a single fertilized egg splits after conception.", "correct_answer": "Monozygotic twins", "incorrect_answers": ["Dizygotic twins", "Conjoined twins", "Twins of two"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the country of Papua New Guinea, how many children does the average woman give birth to during her lifetime according to 2006 estimates?", "correct_answer": "4.6", "incorrect_answers": ["1.2", "2.8", "3.9"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In order to double down in a game of blackjack, your two cards must total exactly what number?", "correct_answer": "Any number", "incorrect_answers": ["Twenty", "Eleven", "Ten"]}]